Please hold onto the side belt of the escalator.
Thank you very much for coming.
Should I get this one? How about this one?
Mami!
What do you think of this?
How about this? This one is good.
Have you decided?
Daddy, don’t be like that.
You're taking too long to decide.
Give her some time to think.
Right?
Yes, Mom! You know me well.
Ok then!
Mami, what are you going to do with those?
I'm trying them on.
All of them?!
Yes, all of them!
Esper Mami - Dancing Dolls upon the Starry Sky
I think I'll get this.
Oh, no! The emergency bell! I got to go!
Where was it...? I found it!
Mami, have you made up your mind?
I'll take this one.
Oh, nice... hey, where are you going?
I'm going to the restroom!
Oops!
That's them...
Hey, everyone!
What happened?
They were there?
Well, they left this.
Oh, no!
They said that they're quitting.
We lost two more members...
What will we do, Hideki?
The kids are waiting. We have to begin.
We don't have enough people.
We'll have to come up with another plan.
Right now?
Yeah.
Excuse me...
I don't mean to be rude, but it looks as if you need some help. I could help you!
What are you all doing here? The kids are waiting.
Okay! Let's do it!
Right!
Could you come with us?
Yes!
Wow! A puppet show!
Hey, this way!
Ok!
Welcome.
Nice to meet you all.
Let's begin.
We'll do it together.
Ms. Sakura Mami, your parents are waiting for you on the second floor lounge room.
Please come to the second floor lounge room.
Please come here, Little Red Riding Hood.
I want to eat her up.
Hi, Grandma.
I brought some wine and flowers for you.
Little Red Riding Hood, I was waiting for you.
Come a little closer. I want to see your face.
Yes, grandma.
No! Don't go!
You'll be eaten!
That's not your grandma, that's a wolf!
What big ears you have, Grandma!
All the better to hear you, my dear.
No!!!
What a big mouth you have, Grandma!
All the better...
...to eat you!
Run, Little Red Riding Hood!
Stupid wolf!
Don't eat her!
How nice! Everyone's into it!
It's so nice...
You fool!
Where have you been?!
I'm sorry!
We were so worried about you.
We were looking for you in every department.
I'm terribly sorry.
Okay, as punishment, I'll skip a meal tonight.
What?
You're skipping dinner?
You'll skip a meal with me?
Konpoko, it's dinner time!
You traitor!
I’m so hungry!
You were in trouble!
It's not funny.
Sorry.
Konpoko was bad, too.
Give me back my mommy.
Megumi, let’s go home.
Mama!
Please, don't be so silly.
What's going on?
I want my mommy back!
She calls her doll, "Mommy".
A doll?
Megumi liked the doll, but I had to throw it away with the trash.
There was a reason I had to...
Give me back my mommy!
I want it, I want it! I want it back...!
Megumi!
Please listen to me.
I'll look for your doll.
Please don't cry, okay?
Wow... this will be hard, but I have to find it.
Will you help me, Konpoko?
What are you doing?
I'm looking for a doll.
I threw it away this morning with the trash.
Where do you live?
Yes. I...
Oh, that area's garbage has already been burned.
No way!
Megumi will understand.
But...
She said there was a reason. Why did Shizu throw the doll away?
I want to know why Megumi calls her doll "Mommy".
I'm going to Megumi's house.
Me, too!
I'm alone again.
Wow, what a big house!
What is this?!
Do you think children will like this plan?
I've told you so many times! What is the purpose of our show?
I want another idea!
Yes sir.
He looks so scary.
Here's your tea.
Thanks.
Megumi's mother passed away six months ago.
Eh?
Since then, Megumi treated her doll as if it was her mother. Her mother made the doll.
It was okay as long as she took good care of the doll. However, she stopped talking to anyone except her doll.
She didn't want to play with her friends. She always stayed in her room.
We had to do something about it. Therefore, I asked Shizu to throw away the doll.
You did it?!
Megumi.
Megumi!
You liar!
Hmm... You want me to make a doll that looks just like this?
Yes!
I could make something similar to it...
However, what her father did would have been undone.
The most important thing for Megumi is for her to face reality.
What can I do?
There could be a way. Let's think about it.
Yeah.
Megumi!
Why are you crying? What are you so sad about?
Oh, I know! It's because you lost the doll your mother made for you, isn't it?
H-How do you know?
I know a lot about you.
Why?
I'm a scary witch. I can change crying children into pumpkins.
Hey, witch! No one is crying!
I know there is someone...
Oh, here's one.
See? She's crying.
Princess Kaguya, please don't cry. She'll turn you into a pumpkin.
But I don't have a mother or father...
Heh, heh... you ARE crying.
I think I hear another crying child.
Witch, no one is crying.
I know there's someone...
Pinocchio, don't cry.
That's my boy!
You're crying so much. I'll be so happy to change you into a pumpkin.
Pinocchio, don't cry.
I can't be human. I don't have a mother or father...
Crying children will become like this!
Witch, you're so mean!
That reminds me, Snow White... You don't have a mother either, right?
Uh...
Aren't you sad?
Yes, but I have...
You have what?
I have... I have the seven dwarfs. I have friends.
They're still not your mother.
How could you say something like that?
See? Now, you're sad. Cry now.
I'll turn you into a pumpkin, too!
Cry!
Cry now!
No! Don't cry!
Please don't disturb us, Megumi. Snow White is about to cry.
No, she won't cry. Isn't that right, Snow White?
Yes, of course!
Yeah! I have my very kind grandfather. I'm not going to cry.
Yes, I have my grandparents, too.
I have... I have my father!
What's going on?!
You're a mean witch! Go away!
Yay! Yay!
Daddy! Daddy!
Yes!
We did it!
That must have been such a nice experience for you.
Yes, it was amazing.
The puppet show is very appealing.
They take good care of the puppets very well.
They clean and fix them every day.
Each puppet has great memories.
It's a dream job.
Well, any job has some hardships...
Oh, you know what? I'm going to make a puppet!
Daddy, can I use your tools?
Ok.
I'll put some clay around the base and make it a pretty dog puppet.
Well... It kinda resembles a cat.
I have to paint it well.
Oops! I put too much paint. Now, it looks funny.
The tail is too big. It looks like a fox.
Oh, I see. This is Konpoko!
Stop it, Konpoko!
Konpoko has no sense of humor.
Konpoko! Wait up, Konpoko!
Konpoko, do you think this puppet can enter the puppet show?
I didn't think I could turn Konpoko into a Panda!
Sorry, sorry!
Right?
Hello!
Please stop!
Here you go.
Please, stop harassing us!
Shut up!
Why do we have to leave?
You'd better leave before someone gets hurt.
I refuse!
What?!
The landlord told us it was okay for us to use this building.
Shut up! Our company purchased this land!
They said they can negotiate as soon as you are gone!
Therefore, you can't stay here any longer.
You stupid guy!
Why...
What's wrong?
You!
Damn... I'll be back!
I don't know what to do anymore!
An earthquake?
Get out of here, or else we'll crush you!
One more time!
Stop it! Stop!
Watch out!
- Get out of my way!
- Do you want to die?
Stop!
What?!
Perverts!!!
What do you mean? You want to quit... all of you?!
Why?
We're going to be married.
But why?
This situation isn't good. We can't get married like this.
If you wonder about the future, you'll know what I'm talking about.
But... you're going to give up your dream?
We promised each other that we'll continue performing wonderful puppet shows!
What about you?
I've thought about it as well, Tomo.
I did enjoy so many things while we were away making so many kids smile.
But...
We can't continue living in this dream!
Please forgive us... Kubo.
I cleaned up all the broken glass.
Sorry... and thank you.
What will you do after this?
Why are they quitting? You guys perform such wonderful puppet shows!
Stop it! We've been doing these since we were students...
I understand them... they put a lot of thought into it.
I'm sorry for yelling...
It’s okay...
I’m so tired...
I'll make some coffee.
No, you wouldn't!
I'm going back to my hometown...
No way! We can find new members and start again!
It'll be the same.
He's right. We can't continue living this dream.
This is the end.
Thank you for helping us.
We've made such nice memories. Thank you.
No... you can't!
I was just thinking about something funny...
What?
Do you remember when we went to the real estate agency to rent the house?
Oh, you want to rent the house. Are you two married?
No. Umm... We're...
We're puppets!
I mean... we make puppet shows together.
Stop laughing so hard.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make you sad...
It's fine.
We'll collect puppets from all over the world and make a one-of-a-kind show!
The train will be leaving soon.
I have to stop him!
I understand you, Mami, but we can't do anything about it!
Hey!
Why?
If we could have stopped him, Tomoko would've stopped him by now!
Tomo, sorry, no... thank you.
I'm fine, but the puppets are...
The puppets?
Tomoko...
This is it... is it really over now?
What can we do about it?
They have given up their dream. There's nothing we can do.
Unless their puppets could talk to them to convince...
That's it! Thank you, Takahata!
Hey, wait up!
Mami, what are you thinking?
A puppet show!
Huh?
Stop crying. This was meant to be.
They abandoned us.
What can we do now? They don't want to make puppet shows any more.
Stop crying now.
Yes, stop it. It's too late to cry now.
What will happen to us?
I don't know. Maybe we'll be thrown in the garbage.
We might get eaten by wild dogs!
Grandpa, does this mean Pinocchio's stories won't be told any more?
Uhh, well...
I want to see the kids again!
Hey, please stop crying. Hideki will come back.
Puppet shows can't be performed by one person.
You are silly!
Tomoko will be there!
Two people aren't enough.
I know they can start again. They have great teamwork.
Wolf, let's wait for them.
I wish I could think like that.
But... do you really think they'll be back?
Yes they will.
He isn't going to give up his dream easily.
He will be back!
Okay, let's wait for him! I'll keep believing in him!
Yes!
Let’s wait! Yes!
Until then, we'll keep performing the shows! We'll have more members soon!
Yes, let's do it!
Let's do it!
Hideki... Hideki...
I don't want to return to the Moon.
I came here to bring you back.
You said we could continue living our dream, but...
...giving up our dream is harder than that.
We have so many dreams that we can share with everyone.
I almost forgot about that.
It may be a little late to tell you this...
If you'll forgive me... we can go back and start again.
I forgive you!
Good for them.
Isn't it good for them, Konpoko?
Hello, this is Sakura.
What? "Kokeshiza"?
Yes, I want them to be in our TV show.
I thought your daughter, Mami, knows them.
What's the matter?
Wake up Mami. I don't know what's going on.
Ok.
Mami!
This feel so good!
We better hurry up before my mother comes to wake me up.
We'll go faster!
Okay!
<i>I'm not suggesting I like you but
<i>you'll find a stolen love letter in your locker
<i>A rumor of romance can draw two people together
<i>Oh, oh, I am sensitive, passionate and still alone
<i>Whistling, I blow a kiss to the summer winds
<i>I tear a page from English dictionary
<i>Through magic, wanted my boyfriend.
<i>Tough luck, that paper plane hit the teacher
<i>Teleportation, my heart's wings
<i>Teleportation, cause the moment to go fast
<i>It's one-sided, and my love has gone unrequited
<i>Teleportation, my heart's wings
<i>Teleportation, cause the moment to go fast
<i>It's one-sided, and my love has gone unrequited